augustint.com 2018-12-30

# Portable TV, Portable Freeview Digital TV, Handheld TV, Bluetooth Speakers, Bluetooth Headphones, Bluetooth Receiver, Bluetooth DAB Radio, Clock Radio, TV Aerial

**Introduction**

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

We value your privacy and in this Privacy Policy, we describe how we collect, use, and disclose information that we obtain about visitors to this website, as well as our other websites. Some features and functionalities (e.g. the ability to make purchases) are not available on our websites; please contact us if you have any questions or are having any difficulties using our site.

By visiting the Site, or using any of our Services, you agree that your personal information will be handled as described in this Policy. Your use of our Site or Services, and any dispute over privacy, is subject to this Policy and our Terms and Conditions (available on this website), including its applicable limitations on damages and the resolution of disputes.

**What information do we collect from our website visitors?**

**How do we use your information?**

**How do we protect your information?**

**Do we use 'cookies'?**

**What about Third Party Advertisers?**

**How we use Google Advertising?**

**What is the California Online Privacy Protection Act (CalOPPA)?**

**What we agree to follow CalOPPA?**

**How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?**

**Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?**

**What is COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)?**

**What is Fair Information Practices?**

**What is the CAN SPAM Act?**

**Why we collect your email address?**

**How to unsubscribe or opt out?**

**What information do we collect from our website visitors?**

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

Provide us with feedback on our products or services. 

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

• To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.

• To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

• To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products

• To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)

**How do we protect your information?**

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

We use regular Malware Scanning.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

**Do we use 'cookies'?**

We are currently using cookies for tracking purposes.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off. Please read our Cookie Policy for more information.

**What about Third Party Advertisers?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety. 

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.

**How we use Google Advertising?**

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en 

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.

**We have implemented the following:**

      • Remarketing with Google AdSense

      • Google Display Network Impression Reporting

      • Demographics and Interests Reporting

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

**Opting out:**

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

**What is the California Online Privacy Protection Act?**

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf

**What we agree to follow CalOPPA:**

Users can visit our site anonymously.

Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.

Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above.

You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:

 • On our Privacy Policy Page

Can change your personal information:

 • By emailing us

 • By logging in to your account

**How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?**

We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

**Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?**

It's also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking

**What is COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)?**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

**What is Fair Information Practices?**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:

We will notify you via email

 • Within 7 business days

We will notify the users via in-site notification

 • Within 7 business days

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

**What is the CAN SPAM Act?**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:

      • Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.

      • Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.

      • Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.

      • Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.

      • Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.

      • Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

**Why we collect your email address?**

We collect your email address in order to:

      • Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions

      • Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.

      • Send you additional information related to your product and/or service

      • Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.

**How to unsubscribe or opt out?**

**If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can opt out at the bottom of our emails**

• Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from  **ALL**  correspondence.

**Contact Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

_www.augustint.com_

Rawmec Business Park Plumpton Rd

Hoddeson, Hertfordshire EN11 0EE

United Kingdom

infouk@augustint.com

01920 487700

Last Edited on 2018-05-23
